Harshita Kaithwas

91+9665374986

kaithwasharshita@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/harshita-kaithwas-133b021a1

Summary

I am Harshita Kaithwas, qualified Technical Support Agent willingness to face challenges in Core IT or relevant. As my area of expertise are in Information & Technology along with Data Analyst for entry level. Proficiency in developing rapid machine learning prototypes and algorithms. Also have ability to take direction and work independently. Passionate individual committed to exploring data and technology. Curious and inquisitive team player completing tasks on time. Strong ability to research and communicate results in clear, professional manner.

Skills

- Ability to turnaround artwork quickly on short notice.
- Exceptional eye for and attention to detail.
- Ability to take direction and work independently.
- Basic knowledge of HTML formatting and HTML5.
- Process improvement
- Microsoft Access
- Structured query language (SQL)

Education

Masters in Computer Management

Dr. Ambedkar College, Nagpur 04/09/2023 – Pursuing

Bachelors in Commerce Computer Application

G.S College of commerce & Economics, Nagpur 09/06/2019 – 8/10/2022

HSC

G.S College of commerce & Economics, Nagpur 2019

SSC

St. Joseph's Covent Girls High School, Nagpur 2017

Certifications

Data Analyst – (Pursuing)
The Maharashtra State Certificate in Information Technology (MSCIT)
Graphic Designing
Tally ERP 9 + GST
3D Animation and Modeling.

Experience

Technical Support Agent - HOTELKEY 12/09/2022 - Current

- Worked with PMS and POS software, helped in problem solving with unique findings.
- Asked customers targeted questions throughout troubleshooting to determine smart solutions.
- Provided clear and concise step-by-step technical support to guide clients.
- Helped customers set up new systems, applications and software.
- Used support tickets to track and speed up incidents.
- Kept detailed records of new installations and related licenses.
- Resolved service user requests within target timeframes.
- Configured networks to meet performance requirements.
- Documented actions taken using work order system within our software.

Customer Relationship Executive - APPLE SERVICE CENTRE 04/07/2022 - 04/09/2022

• Helped customers set up new systems, applications and software.